http://www.earningswhispers.com/privacy_policy

Privacy and Security Policy
EarningsWhispers.com's biggest asset is its registered members and, therefore, it is extremely important for us to maintain your trust. So please be assured that we will never compromise the personal information you provide us. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it.
Privacy Policy
The information you provide for your EarningsWhispers.com account will not be disclose to third parties. EarningsWhispers.com may disclose member information in special cases when we believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) EarningsWhispers.com's rights or property, other EarningsWhispers.com community members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. EarningsWhispers.com may disclose member information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
EarningsWhispers.com does not give, lend, or sell individual information to others, only aggregate information. This aggregate information about our members is shared with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. The data is used to customize the EarningsWhispers.com community and advertising to deliver a better experience for our members.
In case you change your mind or some personal information may change (such as your email address), we will endeavor to provide you a way to correct, update, or remove the personal data you give us. You can do this by contacting our Member Services group at support@earningswhispers.com..
Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you'll see their use by most major web sites.
By showing how and when members us our network, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our members needs.
EarningsWhispers.com has three primary uses for its cookies. First we use cookies to automatically access your previously stored account information when you login to our site in order to deliver a better and more personalized service. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the EarningsWhispers.com network of services that our users find valuable. Finally, our advertising network and third-party advertising networks that serve ads on our site may also use cookies for statistical purposes and for directing members that have clicked on an ad. These cookies do not generally contain personal information. The use of advertising cookies is an industry standard and EarningsWhispers.com does not have access to those cookies used by third-party advertising networks While each of these act ivies depend on the use of a cookie, visitors always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preference.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookies is being sent. However, not that some parts of the EarningsWhispers.com community will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to post messages in our discussion boards.
Financial or portfolio information is never maintained in a cookie.
IP Addresses
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are on the Internet. EarningsWhispers.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When members request pages from the EarningsWhispers.com network, our servers log the members' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that the member's session will be logged, but the member remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our community rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers, or others.
Opting-Out
When you register to join the EarningsWhispers.com community for personalized services, we will send you information about using our community, information about various products and services we provide, or other information we feel may interest you. Only EarningsWhispers.com or a member of the EarningsWhispers.com community network will send you these direct mailings. These e-mails are handled differently than the Whisper Reports we send and we provide the opportunity to opt-out of these emails at the time of registration. If you did not opt-out of these emails at the time of registration, you may do so at anytime by going to http://www.earningswhispers.com/optout.asp
or by emailing optout@earningswhispers.com.
We'll remove your name from our lists as soon as we can (but it may take a little while). Information about unsubscribing from the Whisper Report is contained in the respective mailing and/or in the instructions sent to you after you subscribed to the respective service.
Security
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our members is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, EarningsWhispers.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.
Your EarningsWhispers.com member account is password protected so that only you can access it and view the information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. EarningsWhispers.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information.
Remember to log out of your EarningsWhispers.com account and close your browser when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others or if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet caf.
Links to other sites
Our members should be aware that when you are on EarningsWhispers.com or one of its community sites, you might be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from EarningsWhispers.com's pages that take you outside our service. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use EarningsWhispers.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.
Whenever you give your personal information to these sites, we cannot guarantee the security of the information. EarningsWhispers.com's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond EarningsWhispers.com's control.
Special Offers
Special Offers will be fulfilled by the company making the Special Offer. EarningsWhispers.com will forward your requests for Special Offer(s), along with your e-mail and Special Offer(s) delivery information, to the relevant companies so that they can contact you directly. Once your information is provided to another company pursuant to your request it is not governed by EarningsWhispers.coms privacy policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of each of the companies to determine how your information will be protected.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this site, you signify your assent to the EarningsWhispers.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our community of sites. Your continued use of the EarningsWhispers.com community following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
Last updated 5/15/10
